Look carefully with your heart
You will find the truth is not far
Hey you could or better true and false
Can't escape this soul's gray smoke
Bring all your courage
Maybe then you can save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
Locky was excluded from the case by his uncle
Hawxing found him and told him he had already begun researching an antidote to Dorothy's anesthetic
That night, Mr. K received a strange operation order
The ancient script scholar Yan Xueshi accepted the invitation,
and came to the bank that housed the ancient books and the Eternal Flame
He teamed up with Mr. K to launch a raid
and knocked everyone out with anesthetic
It turned out his true identity
was Lord Eye
The detectives were in danger
Rooftop showdown
My Lord Eye,
Congratulations!
Using a perfect wuxia scheme,
you fooled these ignorant people.
Total victory.
This operation went so smoothly.
Thanks to you, the one from the rebel organization
who infiltrated the enemy.
Ah, Mr. K.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. The earlier betrayal was all a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding.
I know I was wrong.
I hope the all-knowing, all-powerful Lord Eye can forgive my past ignorance.
I report to Lord Eye.
The bomb is ready.
Hmm, use the sacred flames of the bomb to send the pests blocking our way to the next world!
Let's meet up with Shaker at the rendezvous point.
The Illumin-Eye
Shaker.
Sorry, Hawxing.
I warned you.
Strange.
It's been so long.
Why hasn't the bomb exploded yet?
Dorothy.
Why is this?
I don't know.
I definitely set
the bomb to explode in ten minutes.
I'm afraid something's changed.
Dorothy.
Order Shaker to rush over here at once.
A time bomb!
I've returned it to its rightful owner.
So you must be Hawxing, the one who's been opposing us.
A true young hero.
Impressive, impressive.
But what a pity.
What's a pity?
The pity is that today you'll die by my sword.
What are you doing?
Go help them now!
Yes, yes, sir.
I'm preparing to take a shot.
But they keep moving around.
It's hard to aim.
You traitor!
Don't steal my kill!
Locky!
You just recovered from the poison.
Why did you come running here?
How could I let you be the only one in the spotlight?
Is that all you've got?
That's a wrap~
My flawless face!!
Hmph! Come at me if you dare!
Dammit!
The anesthetic hasn't worn off yet.
Hawxing
Give up.
Fighting against us, the Illumin-Eye,
you will never succeed.
Never.
Shaker
Retreat, now!
Hawxing
Why won't you ever listen to my warnings?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
This is all my fault.
I failed to see
Scholar Yan's true identity.
No, it's not your fault.
I'm the one more to blame.
But what's done is done.
What's the point of debating who's right or wrong?
All I know is, as long as we're still breathing,
we must destroy the Illumin-Eye.
Don't push me.
I'm wounded!
My injury is worse than yours.
I think you did it on purpose.
That's right.
When Hawxing attacked me,
you didn't even help.
Do you want me dead?!
You're out of your mind.
You told me not to fight.
And you blew me up.
I haven't settled with you yet.
All of you, shut up!
Your behavior is an utter desecration of love and ideals!
Yes, Lord Eye.
Ending theme
Bright eyes are twinkling
Smiles facing the sun
Bravely speak what's treasured in your heart
That little touch of emotion
A morning breeze blows over
Carrying away a long-held wish
It will quietly be at Zhan Zhan's crossroads
Don't we have a new mission today?
You want to see?
Not even as good as a finger.
This loser's got no money and still comes to drink.
He's asking for it.
What place is this?
This is...
Could this be...